const multipleChoiceQuestions = [
    {
        type: "multipleChoice",
        question: "What is triggered automation?",
        options: [  "An automation that is initiated when a file is dropped into a designated Enhanced FTP Folder", 
                    "An automation that triggers an email to be sent based on a user Initiated Email definition", 
                    "An automation that is initiated when a designated value in a data extension is changed", 
                    "An automation that is triggered based on a schedule that has been defined"],
        answer: "An automation that is initiated when a file is dropped into a designated Enhanced FTP Folder",
    },
    {
        type: "multipleChoice",
        question: "What tool is recommended to render personalization strings, AMPscript, and dynamic content in an email message before sending it to a subscriber?",
        options: [  "List Detective", 
                    "Test Send", 
                    "Send Flow", 
                    "Preview and Test"],
        answer: "Preview and Test",
    },
    {
        type: "multipleChoice",
        question: "Northern Trait Outfitters is using a Smart Capture form on a CloudPage to capture contest registrations in a data extension. Corporate has requested a nightly file with all registrants in this data extension be sent daily from Marketing Cloud to an external SFTP. Which automation configuration should be used to achieve this?",
        options: [  "Schedule Starting Source > Data Extract Activity > File Transfer Activity",
                    "File Drop Starting Source > Data Extract Activity > File Transfer Activity",
                    "Schedule Starting Source > SQL Query Activity > File Transfer Activity",
                    "File Drop Starting Source > SQL Query Activity > File Transfer Activity"],
        answer: "Schedule Starting Source > Data Extract Activity > File Transfer Activity",
    },
    {
        type: "multipleChoice",
        question: "A Marketer developed an email with personalized content based on 5 geographical regions; I. Northwest – Static Image II. Southwest – Image carousel III. Central – No content IV. Northeast – Static image V. Southwest – Coupon, How many dynamic content rules need to be created to accomplish this?",
        options: [  "3",
                    "6",
                    "4",
                    "5"],
        answer: "4",
    },
    {
        type: "multipleChoice",
        question: "A marketer wants to send the same email with the same send properties in several automation. Which activity should be created withinAutomation studio?",
        options: [  "Automated send",
                    "Template send",
                    "Send email",
                    "Triggered send"],
        answer: "Send email",
    },
    {
        type: "multipleChoice",
        question: "After receiving a GDPR “Right to be Forgotten” Request from their compliance team, a marketer must remove a contact from Email Studio. Where should this action be initiated in Marketing Cloud?",
        options: [  "Contact Builder > Contacts Configuration",
                    "Administration > Contacts",
                    "Contact Builder > All Contacts",
                    "Email Studio > All Subscriber"],
        answer: "Contact Builder > All Contacts",
    },
    {
        type: "multipleChoice",
        question: "What can be used to join two data extensions to segment via Drag and Drop Segmentation?",
        options: [  "Subscriber Key",
                    "Data Relationship",
                    "Subscriber ID",
                    "Send Relationship"],
        answer: "Data Relationship",
    },
    {
        type: "multipleChoice",
        question: "A marketer wants to send an email to a sendable data extension that contains a Customer_ID field with a numeric data type that relates to the subscriber key on the all subscriber list as a send relationship. Which two statements are correct about the email send behaviour for any subscriber who currently does not exist on the all subscriber list?",
        options: [  "The email address and subscriber key will be added to the all subscriber list.",
                    "The subscriber will be added to the all subscriber list with a status of Active.",
                    "If the customer_ID field does not exist on the all subscriber list, the email send will fail.",
                    "The primary key and demographic data will be added to the All subscriber list."],
        answer: "The email address and subscriber key will be added to the all subscriber list.",
    },
    {
        type: "multipleChoice",
        question: "Northern Trail Outfitters (NTO) offers a 90-day trial on weekly snack box subscriptions. NTO would like to send out a series of emails to educate and remind members to purchase the subscription before the trial ends. What tool is an option for this scenario?",
        options: [  "Content Builder",
                    "Guided Send",
                    "Send Flow",
                    "Automation Studio"],
        answer: "Automation Studio",
    },
    {
        type: "multipleChoice",
        question: "While testing an email with dynamic content in Content Builder, proofs of five content variations need to be reviewed directly in the inbox of a marketer's quality assurance specialist and the marketing manager. A data extension named 'myTestData' contains only the variations needed. Which method should be used to accomplish this task?",
        options: [  "Enter the email addresses to receive proofs, and then choose to send ,Based on Subscriber Preview 'myTestData.''",
                    "Choose data extension of contacts, and then choose to send 'Based on Recipient Test Data Extension.'",
                    "Enter the email addresses to receive proofs, and then select the specific records from a list or data extension whose rendering should be sent.",
                    "Create a Test data extension that contains the five content variations the two team members need to validate"],
        answer: "Enter the email addresses to receive proofs, and then choose to send ,Based on Subscriber Preview 'myTestData.''",
    },
    {
        type: "multipleChoice",
        question: "The marketing team at a bank needs to receive a file of all subscribers who were sent payment reminder emails and opened them each week. The file needs to be encrypted and placed on the bank's external SFTP. How should the scheduled automation be configured to achieve this?",
        options: [  "Filter Activity > File Transfer Activity > Data Extract Activity",
                    "Filter Activity > Query Activity > File Transfer Activity",
                    "Query Activity > Data Extract Activity > File Transfer Activity",
                    "Data Extract Activity > Query Activity > File Transfer Activity"],
        answer: "Query Activity > Data Extract Activity > File Transfer Activity",
    },
    {
        type: "multipleChoice",
        question: "A 15-person management team wants to review test emails built in Email Studio prior to live deployment based on content that is personalized for them, but is clearly noted as a test email. What is the safest, most effective way for a marketer to accomplish this task without compromising the email content?",
        options: [  "Find each individual with Subscriber Preview and Test Send to each individual Recipient.",
                    "Create a list composed of the management team, prepend “Test” to the Subject, and use the Send Flow to send the email to the list.",
                    "Create a data extension composed of the management team, create a User-Initiated Send Definition, select the email, prepend “Test” to the Subject, select the data extension, and send the email.",
                    "Create a Test data extension composed of the management team and Test Send to the Test data extension"],
        answer: "Create a Test data extension composed of the management team and Test Send to the Test data extension",
    },
    {
        type: "multipleChoice",
        question: "A marketer for Northern Trail Outfitters needs to share multiple assets in  Content Builder for a campaign with another business unit in their account. How should the marketer share these assets?",
        options: [  "Move the content into the Shared Content folder in Content Builder.",
                    "Create and share a new folder for the assets in Content Builder.",
                    "Individually share each asset with the other business unit in Content Builder.",
                    "Switch to Classic Content to move the assets into the Shared Content folder."],
        answer: "Move the content into the Shared Content folder in Content Builder.",
    },
    {
        type: "multipleChoice",
        question: "A marketer wants to ensure that customers on a list want to be email subscribers. Additionally, the marketer wants to minimize the number of invalid email addresses on the list, and add a level of security when using Web Collect functionality. What is the optimal way to accomplish this task?",
        options: [  "Create a double opt-in campaign that requires subscribers to confirm their email address by clicking a link in an email they receive after subscribing via Web Collect",
                    "Add new subscribers to an automated engagement campaign, and then send a series of welcome emails based on their opens and clicks",
                    "Configure Web Collect to return an error message for any email address that does not conform to standard conventions",
                    "Send a welcome email to subscribers within 24 hours that includes a link to the website, a link to the terms and conditions page, and a customer service number"],
        answer: "Create a double opt-in campaign that requires subscribers to confirm their email address by clicking a link in an email they receive after subscribing via Web Collect",
    },
    {
        type: "multipleChoice",
        question: "",
        options: [  "",
                    "",
                    "",
                    ""],
        answer: "",
    },
    {
        type: "multipleChoice",
        question: "",
        options: [  "",
                    "",
                    "",
                    ""],
        answer: "",
    },
    {
        type: "multipleChoice",
        question: "",
        options: [  "",
                    "",
                    "",
                    ""],
        answer: "",
    },
    {
        type: "multipleChoice",
        question: "",
        options: [  "",
                    "",
                    "",
                    ""],
        answer: "",
    },
    {
        type: "multipleChoice",
        question: "",
        options: [  "",
                    "",
                    "",
                    ""],
        answer: "",
    },
    {
        type: "multipleChoice",
        question: "",
        options: [  "",
                    "",
                    "",
                    ""],
        answer: "",
    }
];
